REN DUO

CONTACT

+1 929 996 4225

jerrickren@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jerrick-ren-123729a1/



New York, USA

SKILLS

Critical Skills: Python | Bloomberg Terminal| SQL | VBA|R| Advanced MS Office

Core Skills: Negotiation | Global Strategy | Project Management | Digital literacy

EDUCATION

Lehigh University

Master of Business Administration-Business Analytics

2022-2023

China University of Geosciences

Bachelor of Mechanical design and manufacture 2010-2014

LANGUAGES

English | Mandarin | Finnish

OTHERS (CERTIFICATE):

- · Google Analytics Certification
- PMI-Project Management Certificate
- Asian Ambassador ---- HundrED (2020-2022) (A Finland based global leading edtech non-profit organization)
- External Advisor On Global Expansion —- Blue Elephant Capital

PROFILE

Seven years of experience in marketing and international expansion for corporations, unicorn companies and high-growth startups in the technology industry. General managed the biggest Edtech gathering in Asia (Global Education Technology); Proven success in helping 10+ Chinese Edtech companies expand to global markets; 5+ overseas companies localization in the Asian market and increase clients' ROI through strategic planning, consulting, and marketing advisory services.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Head of Overseas

JMD

Mar 2019 - Jun2022 Helsinki, Finland-Singapore-New York, USA

- Supervised overseas growth strategy, product marketing and social media campaigns for partner Unicorn Edtech companies: Duolingo, 51Talk, and Netease-Youdao.
- Supported venture capital investments, partnerships, and research into Tech companies and Edtech startups across China, Singapore, Vietnam, the United States and Australia.
- Developed growth strategies through lead generation and community operation.
- Overall management for overseas sponsor collaboration and overseas speaker recruitment for GET (Global Education Technology) Summit Expo, the largest Edtech gathering in Asia. (GET 2019 gathered 12000+ attendees from 42 countries.)
- Gave speeches at Edtech gatherings globally about China's Edtech Market trends and development (Edtech Asia 2018-2019, Edtech Europe 2017, etc.)
- Built and lead JMDEdu's overseas marketing, editorial and business development team.

Overseas Business Development Director

JMD

Jan 2017- Mar 2019 Beijing, China

- Developed new business relationships with the overseas government, EdTech, SaaS, and growth-oriented, tech-enabled services businesses in emerging growth economies globally.
- Acted as the liaison that facilitated and led strategic investments in high-quality assets in the educational sector in overseas markets.
- Initiated and coordinated with stakeholders to make a 2\$ million strategic investment in Edsurge, the largest Edtech media platform in the U.S.
- Enhanced JMDEdu and GET (Global Education Technology) global brand impact through business development activities in the global Edtech ecosystem and represented JMDEdu across 30+ conferences and summits in China / HK, India, Finland, UK, Germany, Vietnam, Singapore, and USA.

Marketing Supervisor

Cheac

Aug 2014 - Sep 2016 Beijing, China

- Managed all Greater China lead generation through media buying, organizing online / offline events, webinars, and digital advertising.
- Organized overseas universities' alum networks in China, planned and executed in-country orientation or recruitment, and ensured institutions obtained their global diversity and enrollment goals.

PROJECT:

- Alibaba Buyer Community-Centrality Analysis and Strategy MKT325 -Consumer Insights through Data Analysis
- S&P 500 sentiment index analysis- FIN377-GBUS421-Advanced Investment (Python)